The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
These Fire Spirit Beasts are endless !
Our top priority is to activate the Country Sealing Formation.
Otherwise, even if we flee to Xuanwu,
the Fire Spirit Beasts will follow us
and the country of Xuanwu will also be burned to the ground.
Senior Brother Song is right,
we should act fast.
Order the army to cross the border at all costs !
After we activate the Country Sealing Formation,
we will invade Xuanwu together !
Hold on ! If we can't cross,
then the Burning Fire Alliance will perish here !
What is this ?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Everyone, be careful !
What are they doing ?
What is this ?
What the hell is this?
Those beasts have... mutated !
The Fire Spirit Beasts are growing stronger,
we need to cross now !
Charge !
Follow me!
Let's do this !
Big brother !
Big...
brother...
Wan'er...
No...
Brother...
Brother !
The Fire Spirit Beasts come from here.
Sealing this place should restrain these beasts.
By using the Country Sealing Formation,
we can trap all the Fire Spirit Beasts within the Burning Fire country.
Fellow cultivators, let's begin.
Fellow rogue cultivators,
we cannot operate this formation without you.
We need Nascent Soul cultivators
to use their Nascent Soul as fuel for the formation.
It's the only way we have to seal the country.
It's alright,
we'll just lose a hundred years of spiritual energy.
Since you are offering Spirit Restoration Pills,
Then we will do our best for the Burning Fire Alliance !
Fellow cultivators, focus on operating the formation.
My sect
will protect your physical bodies.
I guarantee you
that we will have established ourselves in Xuanwu in 3 months.
When we succeed,
I will personally come to welcome you all back.
The Country Sealing Formation is activating ! Hurry up !
Is this the Country Sealing Formation ?
Let's see what they can do now.
If the Fire Beasts are already this powerful,
then I wonder how terrifying it would've been
with the Fire Spirit Beast King.
Brother Qiqing, fortune favors the brave.
Junior Sister Muwan,
we are at the border of Xuanwu,
you must stay focused.
Country of Xuanwu
Clear Heart Sect Ancestor
Ancestor,
I heard that the Burning Fire country is in shambles.
Isn't it amusing ?
Let's just watch the spectacle.
When two tigers fight,
we can just reap the benefits.
What's happening ?
Fellow cultivators,
what does this mean !?
Clear Heart Sect disciples,
follow me to retreat and seek reinforcements !
Hurry up !
You can't escape.
You dared to violate the peace between our countries.
Xuanwu's 50 major sects won't let that slide !
Your Clear Heart Sect also stole that mountain once.
It's just changing owners once again today.
The Ancestor is dead !
Retreat, quickly !
Retreat !
Unaware of your limits ?
Break !
You can’t defend Heng Yue Mountain.
Instead of letting others claim it,
give it to my Xuan Dao Sect.
Isn't this just the law of the jungle again ?
Listen up.
During the Fire Spirit Beast attack,
the sects of Xuanwu ignored our pleas for help
and watched from the side.
They hoped that
they would reap benefits from our loss.
We have no choice
but to fight for our survival !
For this war,
every cultivator will be given an artifact.
Foundation Establishment cultivators will get a Core Formation artifact
and Core Formation cultivators will get a Nascent Soul artifact.
All the items you steal will be yours.
The Alliance won't confiscate anything.
Burning Fire Alliance !
I should be able to find a way to escape
amidst the chaos of this war.
All the disciples
will also be given
a jade slip like this one.
This jade records your kill count.
For every 100 5th layer of Qi Condensation or above kills,
you will get 10 mid-quality spirit stones.
For every 20 Foundation Establishment kills,
you will get 10 bottles of pills.
These are good rules,
they're based on your contribution.
Watch me slaughter my way through Xuanwu.
We'll get hundreds of spirit stones !
Conflict never ends in this chaotic world...
Who knows if we will ever find true peace.
Everyone,
the Luo River Sect has other rewards.
Each month, the person with the most kills will get a Heaven Separating Pill.
The Luo River Sect is really going all out !
Did I hear correctly ?
A Heaven Separating Pill !?
With a Heaven Separating Pill
and with the Underworld Ascension Method,
I'm 80% confident I can reach Core Formation.
After that, I'll be the strongest under Nascent Soul...
Alright, the war is about to begin.
All Burning Fire Alliance disciples
will report to their assigned squad leader.
Understood !
Wang Lin, I have the map Lin Tao copied.
I will give you the first piece now.
If you kill 50 Foundation Establishment cultivators,
I will give you the second piece.
If you can kill
150 Foundation Establishment cultivators,
I will give you the last piece.
There is no room for negotiation here...
It's either kill for rewards
or die on the battlefield.
The Ancestor played her cards well.
Zhang Zili
Evil Devil Sect disciple
Early stage Core Formation
The 10th squad has begun attacking the Spirit Vein
so Xuanwu will surely send reinforcements.
Our 8th squad's mission
is to intercept anyone passing within 500 li.
Now spread out.
If you spot anyone,
notify me immediately.
Yes squad leader !
With my Early stage Core Formation cultivation,
I should be attacking sects in the 1st squad.
This mission is too boring...
Here, Burning Fire Alliance cultivators !
Let's kill them all !
Kill them !
The reinforcements have arrived,
it's too late for you to leave now !
You will die here !
You were fated to die by the Fire Spirit Beasts,
stop clinging to your life !
Foundation Establishment brat,
the moment I get out of this,
I will skin you alive
and rip out your heart !
It looks like this bloody war is unavoidable.
This flying sword is strange. Retreat !
Where do you think you're going ?
How did this kid kill them ?
Even I couldn't have killed 7 of them instantly.
But he's just Middle stage Foundation Establishment...
No !
He must be hiding his cultivation.
Over 100 cultivators are approaching from behind.
8th squad, retreat to the Spirit Vein !
Above the Spirit Vein
Country of Xuanwu
Attack !
Kill them !
Burning Fire Alliance, charge !
Fight to the death !
Drive them out of Xuanwu !
Come,
bring it on !
Ancestor, we are suffering heavy losses.
Xuan Jia
Shennong Hall disciple
Early stage Core Formation
Hong Tian
Shennong Hall Ancestor
Even though he's only Foundation Establishment,
he uses strange spells and artifacts.
Go, kill him.
Understood.
Late stage Foundation Establishment ? They can't beat me.
Master really is unmatched below Core Formation.
But you still need to be careful when operating solo.
What if a Core Formation cultivator appears ?
Xuan Jia, go !
You're just relying on your artifacts.
I will put your miserable life to an end !
Damn rat ! Do you have any other spell
than your Earth Escape Technique !?
Invader, I'll take your life !
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?